Guide to the Lester R. Armstrong Photographs circa 1917-1957
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
- Wishers, McPherson: Dayton, Washington, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1680)
- Wishing well, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1752)
- Wishing well, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1753)
- Woodpecker, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1754)
- Woods, Willis E., 1942 September (Box 5, Folder 1755)
- Work bench, Circa 1953 (Box 5, Folder 1756)
- Worm, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1757)
- Worth, Elizabeth [African American], Undated (Box 5, Folder 1758)
- Wray, Ruth, 1949 October 13 (Box 5, Folder 1759)
- Wrecks: Auto, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1760)
- Wrecks: Train, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1761)
- Wrestlers, women, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1774)
- Wrestling, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1763)
- Wrestling, 1946 January 10 (Box 5, Folder 1764)
- Wrestling: Armstrong, Jack, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1762)
- Wrestling: Jumping Joe Savoldi, 1947 March 3 (Box 5, Folder 1765)
- Wright: Brother and sister portraits, 1950 April 9 (Box 5, Folder 1766)
- Wrights, Shirley, 1953 May 9 (Box 5, Folder 1767)
- Wrights, Shirley, 1954 May 29 (Box 5, Folder 1768)
- Yeager, Dick: Baby, 1950 March 23 (Box 5, Folder 1769)
- Yenney, C.F., 1945 December 9 (Box 5, Folder 1770)
- Yosemite, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1771)